Last Updated: August 12, 2020

By registering your details with us you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to the provisions of this 
Privacy Policy and to our Terms of Service. Cabinet Solutions On line privacy statement discloses the privacy 
practices as a site hosted by Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. Because maintaining the trust of our users is a priority 
to us, Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. is committed to respecting your privacy. Cabinet Solutions mission is to build user 
'trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  We want to demonstrate 
our commitment to your privacy. Cabinet Solutions Software, LLC. welcomes your feedback about this privacy policy. Send your 
questions or concerns regarding our privacy statement to [support@cabinetsolutions.net](mailto:support@cabinetsolutions.net). 

CABINET SOLUTIONS DESIGN SOFTWARE, LLC. WILL NEVER SELL YOUR INFORMATION OR GIVE YOUR INFORMATION TO ANY OTHER COMPANY OTHER THAN TO 
PARTNER CABINET SOLUTIONS DESIGN SOFTWARE, LLC. COMPANIES AND ONLY IF THAT COMPANY NEEDS YOUR INFORMATION TO BENEFIT YOUR COMPANY IN 
THE USE OF CABINET SOLUTIONS SOFTWARE.

1. What is Cabinet Solutions Online's product and why is my information needed?

   Cabinet Solutions is an online managed service that allows perform product demonstrations and securely share 
   confidential information from anywhere, anytime. Because Cabinet Solutions is Web based, it requires the use of 
   first and last names, billing contact information, and a valid email address. Therefore, at a minimum, we require 
   such necessary information during the registration process.

2. What information does Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. gather/track and how is it used?

   PERSONAL INFORMATION: Because of the nature of our product, we must collect personal information from users during 
   the registration process, including (at minimum) first and last names, an email address, and billing contact 
   information. Your email address may be used to send you periodic newsletters from Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. and it 
   may be used by us on the behalf of third-party advertisers, but only upon your express consent.

   We use the information collected to deliver services, process payments, update our records, communicate with you 
   about products and services and generally maintain your accounts with us.

   Because of our commitment to present the best possible product to all our users, we track the category of services 
   selected by our individual users as well as all information pertaining to user satisfaction. To ensure the quality 
   of our product, we reserve the right to maintain evaluation and feedback records.

   PARTNERS: In some cases we provide services or sell product lines jointly with other businesses. For these 
   co-branded offerings in which a third party is involved in your transactions, we will sometimes share or jointly 
   collect customer information related to those transactions with that third party. 

   SECURITY INFORMATION: Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. also collects certain standard information about your computer for 
   security and identification purposes. This information may include: IP addresses, domain names and other uniquely 
   identifying information of machines that have the Cabinet Solutions software downloaded and installed. This 
   information is used for the operation of the service, to identify and protect our customers and to control 
   unauthorized use or abuse of our services. All information is stored securely within our servers.

   SURVEYS: In addition to required member information, we may conduct surveys and ask users to volunteer demographic 
   information to be used on an aggregate basis for internal market research, presentation to advertisers and joint 
   research projects with partner companies involved in product development. We use such information to better focus 
   our product and personalize the scope of services offered to each individual user. Such information will not be 
   passed to third parties without your prior consent unless where required by applicable law.

3. With whom does Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. share the information?

   Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. products and services by necessity require us to provide some of your information to third 
   parties. We may occasionally employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing 
   credit card payments, sending postal mail. They have access to personal information needed only to perform their 
   functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Further, they must process the personal information in 
   accordance with this Privacy Policy.

   Occasionally we send offers to select groups of Cabinet Solutions customers on behalf of partner businesses. When 
   we do this, we do not share your personal information with the other businesses. Except in the limited instances 
   as stated above, we will never voluntarily share personally identifiable information with any third party without 
   the user's express consent or unless compelled by applicable state and federal laws. Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. does 
   not control the practices of our affiliates. If you have questions about how affiliates use the information 
   gathered when you link to them, please read their privacy policies.

4. How can I review, correct and update my personal information?

   If you wish to change your personal information, email your company name, address, and your name as well as updated 
   information to [support@cabinetsolutions.net](mailto:support@cabinetsolutions.net). NEVER UPDATE YOUR CREDIT CARD INFO BY EMAIL. You can also change your 
   email status to receive our newsletter, email marketing communications and third-party promotions administered by 
   Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. Please contact us at [support@cabinetsolutions.net](mailto:support@cabinetsolutions.net) if you need assistance in updating your 
   information.

5. How does Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. protect my information from loss, misuse or alteration?

   Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. uses industry-standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of personally identifiable 
   information, including password protection and firewalls.

   Furthermore, Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. is not liable for loss of passwords due to user carelessness. If you lose 
   control over your password, you may lose control over your personally identifiable information. If you believe 
   your password has been compromised, we recommend that you immediately change your password by contacting 
   Cabinet Solutions at 209-836-4077. 

6. Who can I ask if I have additional questions?

   For additional inquiries about the privacy of your information, you can contact Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC. via email 
   at [support@cabinetsolutions.net](mailto:support@cabinetsolutions.net) by calling (209) 836-4077 or by writing to us via regular mail at: 

      Cabinet Solutions Design Software, LLC.
      11081 Old Number Six Hwy. Eutawville, SC 29048
